module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Who composed the 1998 hit song "Blue (Da Ba Dee)"?', 
    a: 'Tal Bachman',
    b: 'Blink 182',
    c: 'Eiffel 65',
    d: 'Paris 35',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is a popular Filipino fast food franchise?', 
    a: 'Tim Hortons',
    b: 'Jollibee',
    c: 'Yo! Sushi',
    d: 'FEBO',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What city in Colorado was named after a valuable ore compound?', 
    a: 'Telluride',
    b: 'Granada',
    c: 'La Veta',
    d: 'Castle Rock',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these business is NOT owned by Amazon?', 
    a: 'Zappos',
    b: 'Audible',
    c: 'IMDB',
    d: 'Hulu',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who played Mary Katherine Gallagher in the film "Superstar"?', 
    a: 'Tina Fey',
    b: 'Rachel Dratch',
    c: 'Molly Shannon',
    d: 'Amy Poehler',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Entomology is the study of what?', 
    a: 'Insects',
    b: 'Words',
    c: 'Ocean',
    d: 'Trees',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What weapon does Raphael, the Ninja Turtle, use?', 
    a: 'Sword',
    b: 'Nunchuck',
    c: 'Sai',
    d: 'Bo',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What tool is also known as a "hex key"?', 
    a: 'Allen Wrench',
    b: 'Torque Wrench',
    c: 'Gavel',
    d: 'Drill Bit',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Hannibal\'s army famously crossed the Alps riding what animal?', 
    a: 'Yaks',
    b: 'Elephants',
    c: 'Donkeys',
    d: 'Mules',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many months of the year have 30 days?', 
    a: 'Four',
    b: 'Five',
    c: 'Six',
    d: 'Seven',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];